when I talk about how d m s O has helped
me get blood flow in my scar tissue
this is what I'm talking about
this is the top of my foot here
this is the lower part of my leg
the scarring goes up along here
and then all down in here
and you can kind of see how it's kind of brown
in here  I actually quit putting d m s O on my lower
leg so that it would turn brown again
so you can see what I'm talking about  so
I was in a bad wreck
ten years ago
little over 10 years ago
this part of my leg was pretty
much completely crushed
and the doctors who operated on me saved my leg
I'm very thankful for that
they took a lot of the connective tissue from the top
of my foot and turned it around and used it in here
I had multiple skin grafts and that's
you can tell the skin grafts leave
this kind of funky skin right here
and then I've got these places
where the skin didn't quite
grow back quite like what they wanted
but this was a really difficult
place for them to get it to
actually grow back
because the just this blood
flow was just not happening
before I started using the DMSO
I tried lots of different things to help with
the circulation and some things worked some
but not great
where you can see it's kind of brown and yucky here
this was actually all the way down throughout my foot
all the way across this scar on the top of my foot
and then this area which you can see
pretty well  it's pretty brown and gray looking
it had it had actually turned pretty much
completely gray before I started using the DMSO
and then this area down here see
how it's real purpley that
that just stayed dark purple
and brown and gray looking
it was it was gross
the blood flow issue has been
ongoing for the last 10 years  I needed
to get the blood flowing in this in this
scar tissue consistently and well  that's
why I thought well I'll try the
DMSO and see what happens
these are photos I took 2 weeks after
using the DMSO and aloe Vera mix daily
you can see that it really increased the
blood flow into that scarred area
something else happened that really surprised me
most of this has been numb
completely numb on the surface and underneath
I have feeling up in here
I have feeling on my toes
I have feeling
because they use those nerves
here and replace them here
I have feeling
if I run my finger across the scar here
I can feel it across the tops of my toes over there
it's very strange feeling
but it's there
so after I was using the DMSO for several days
I went for a walk and I
realized I could feel my ankle
I could feel the pressure on my ankle as I walked
which is something I hadn't felt in at that point
nine and a half years
I thought well that's odd
and then when I got home
I started running my fingers over the scarring
and I realized I could feel a lot more
like this whole area hasn't had feeling
nine and a half years
and I can now run my fingers across this and feel it
I can now run my fingers across
my foot here and feel it  I still
a lot of this is still numb
this is starting to get feeling
which is really surprising
considering all the damage that was there
I have feeling on the edges of this scar tissue
that haven't been there in nine and a/2 years  so
I'm really surprised and pleased about that